https://www.kimber.com/about/privacy-policy

Privacy Policy
This Privacy Statement describes how RKB Industrial and its group companies including Kimber Kable, Heatshrink.com, WattGate, WBT USA ("we", "us" and "our") use any information from which any individual can be identified, such as names, contact details and ID data ("Personal Information"). At Kimber Kable, we believe that the Personal Information you provide to us must be kept confidential and used in a responsible fashion. We consistently strive to put our best efforts towards achieving both of these objectives.
Kimber Kable is committed to safeguarding all Personal Information we receive either directly from you or that has been provided to us from any third party ("you" and "your"). To the extent that any Personal Information is collected, it will be held in confidence in accordance with the Data Protection Legislation (as defined below). Please read the following Privacy Statement which explains how we use and protect your information.
We will only use Personal Information which is provided to us, or otherwise obtained by us, as set out in this Statement. We will ensure that your Personal Information is handled in accordance with the "Data Protection Legislation" (meaning any law applicable from time to time relating to the processing of Personal Information and/or privacy as the same may be re-enacted, applied, amended, superseded, repealed or consolidated in any jurisdiction to which we are subject, including without limitation, the UK Data Protection Act 1998, the General Data Protection Regulation (EU) 2016/679 (with effect from 25 May 2018), and the Privacy and Electronic Communications (EC Directive) Regulations 2003, CAN SPAM Act of 2003, in each case including any legally binding regulations, directions and orders issued from time to time under or in connection with any such law).
For the purposes of the Data Protection Legislation, Kimber Kable is the entity that determines for which and the manner in which any Personal Information that you provide to us or we otherwise obtain about you is or is to be processed.
